http://www.scootersoftware.com/index.php?zz=kb_privacy

HomeFeaturesDownloadPurchaseSupport
Privacy Statement
Our Commitment
Scooter Software is committed to protecting your privacy.
We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
Our website is structured so that you can visit and download trial software without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.
If you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your customer relationship with Scooter Software.
IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE you are not allowed to participate in the Scooter Software forums, or to provide any personal information on our site.
Forum Registration
Scooter Software encourages users who want to participate in the Scooter Software support forums to register.
In order to register, you must provide us with a username (which does not have to be your real name), password and a valid email address.
This allows us to protect our community from abusive postings and provides a verifiable point of contact should legal questions arise.
At any time, you have the ability to keep your email address hidden from other users by selecting that option within your user profile.
When you register, you have the option of providing some additional information such as occupation, interests, and homepage URL.
This optional information is made available to other bulletin or message board users to foster a sense of community.
If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave the fields blank and your registration will still be processed.
Ordering Online
When you place an online order, we need to know your name, email address, phone number, billing address and credit card details.
This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.
Our online shop uses a secure server.
The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us.
The customer data and orders we collect are protected against unauthorized access.
Disclosure to Outside Parties
Scooter Software does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
Scooter Software may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-parties, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.
Scooter Software may release account information to (a) comply with law, (b) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (c) protect the rights, property or safety of Scooter Software, our users, or others.
Your Consent
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Scooter Software.
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Regardless of any changes we make to our privacy policy, we will always use your personal information in accordance with the version of the policy in place at the time you provided your information, unless you give your express consent for us to do otherwise.
GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION - GDPR
Scooter Software's collection and handling of Personal Identifiable Information (PII) is compliant with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
To exercise your GDPR rights to request your PII or request your PII is erased, please contact us.
Scooter SoftwareAbout UsContact UsTimeline: Our First 20 YearsOur TeamCareersGallery NightCompany, Product LogosPrivacy PolicyLegal Notices
Copyright © 2020 Scooter Software, Inc.
Contact UsJobsPrivacy PolicyLegal Notices
